ANNOUNCER:
Guess what, Pin?
You've won a Win Token.
What is a Win Token?
As you remember, you were
the only one to rip the ribbon.
That means you did better than
the rest of the contestants,
so you win a Win Token.
If you're about to get eliminated,
you can use your Win Token
to void half of your votes.
And here's your Win Token.
Now it's time for Cake at Stake.
♪ Da-da-da-da-da-da ♪
♪ Cake at Stake! ♪
But first we have to get...
Get into your teams, people.
OK, Squashy Grapes.
You lost last time, so you do the Cake at Stake.
Sit.
I have nine slices of cake.
If you receive a slice of cake,
you get to stay for another day.
If you don't, you leave the battle.
But don't worry. You'll be treated with TLC.
OK, let's see how many votes we received.
Seven votes.
Now it's time to pass out the cake.
Leafy, you got zero votes. Here's your cake.
Needle, you also got zero votes.
Same with Ice Cube,
Rocky,
Teardrop,
and Coiny.
Uh, maybe I should turn down
the throwing speed of the tosser.
Snowball, you're safe at zero, too.
Tennis Ball, you didn't do anything good, but...
you're safe with one vote.
So is "sam!", whoever Sam is.
If you kick me out,
I'll CRUSH you with my Announcer Crusher!
Well, too bad for me,
because Golf Ball is safe at one vote.
- ANNOUNCER: And you, Flower, are out with four votes.
- FLOWER: GRRRRRRRR!
FLOWER:
WHAAAAAOOWWHAAA!!!!!
Earlier this morning, I was
really afraid of being POPPED,
but now I'm feeling better and
I don't think I'm gonna be popped!
WOO!
Now my chances of winning went up
from 5% to 5.263%!
Wow, GB. I'm impressed.
No arms, and you can still use a calculator!
What made you think I was using a calculator?
♪ [INTRO PLAYS] ♪
Subtitles: Daniel Adam Valle
The second contest is an obstacle course.
You have an hour to complete it.
When you get to the end, you will try
to get as much water into your team tank
as you can in the remaining amount of time.
At the end of the hour,
whichever team has more water wins.
And yes, whoever is the first
to finish the course gets a Win Token.
Wait.
Before that O get onto the screen,
I have to tell you one more thing.
AWWWH.
BOOOOOOOORRRRRRING.
Cherries, you're missing a team member.
If you don't find that team member
in the next hour, your team automatically loses.
BLOCKY!
OK, O, come on over.
Squishy Cherries! Stop!
We have to decide who will find Blocky
and who will run the course.
We'll find Blocky.
PIN:
Spongy, you go too.
And, Pencil, go with them!
But, our alliance!
We have to stick together!
Alliance, shmalliance. Go, GO!
Pencil! We'll wait for you!
Whoa! In first!
WHOA!
Oof!
Oh, great.
OK, so THIS is the fish that ate Blocky.
Now we have to get him out.
Wow, Needle! She's such a fast runner.
That's good!
PBBT!
GRR!
AUGH!
OMQ, what is taking her so long?
Be patient. It's only been five minutes or so!
♪ Open mouth, yeah, yeah, yeah! ♪
♪ Let him out, yeah, yeah, yeah! ♪
- BLOCKY: What is she doing?
- PENCIL: ♪ So we can win the contest, ♪
- PEN: Blocky! I thought you got eaten!
- PENCIL: ♪ so we can win the contest! ♪
No. It tried to eat me,
but it missed me by A BIT!
WAAAAOOOOUUUUGH!
♪ Come on and open that-  ♪
YEAH!
Yikes!
I'm stuck!
Sorry, Pin.
Please don't tell me Woody will have to climb me!
WOODY:
Auuuweuuerrr...
Ehhhhh...
AHHHH!
Jump, Rocky!
TB! What in the spherical world was THAT for?
To prevent a Rocky and Woody collision.
GOLF BALL:
Okay.
TB, Help me!
Thank you!
But now I can't cross!
Aw, seriously?
Thanks for all you're doing for me.
No problem.
HNNNGHHH!
AAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHH!
NEEDLE:
Aw, seriously?
Well, here we go!
Hey, watch this!
The bowling ball and you
are falling at the SAME RATE!
Need a break from all the stress?
Then eat our gumball.
It's only 70,000 payments
of $70,000.
Each.
Call now. The number on your screen.
Now.
BLOCKY:
Here's a fun prank you can pull!
Drill a hole into the Bubble Recovery Center,
pour tacks in,
and watch Bubble pop INFINITELY!
HA ha-ha ha-ha! HA ha-ha-ha...
This program was brought to you
by Blocky's Funny Doings International.
OMZ!
I killed her!
Oh, well.
Easy.
AAAAAAAAHHHHH!
Okay, let's get back now.
We have a BUNCH of lost time to make up!
Oh!
OMW. Spongy.
He just makes me wanna HURL.
MATCH:
Pencil, you're here!
Now let's go, SUPER FAST!
Oh, thank you, you're here!
GET ME OVER THAT WALL!
Over THAT?!
I dunno...
Still stuck!
Arms might be useful right about NOW!
FINALLY!
Huh? NO, WOOOOAH!
MATCH:
And THROW!
PEN:
Oof!
Well, THAT'S convenient!
Hey, Firey!
OW! Grr!
COINY:
Hey!
Throw us up!
Yeah, but nah.
We're only going for our own team...
Spongy.
Yeah!
Uh-oh.
Ugh! ARGH! Come ON!
Help us up!
Golf Ball! Look!
Huh? Oh, great, the balls are here.
TD, help me get more ahead of Firey!
Water. It's TOO DANGEROUS to handle!
Uh oh!
I'm stuck!
Heh-heh. Thanks, TB and GB.
MATCH:
We gotta go, Pencil.
Oh, no! I've been DULLED!
Spongy!
BUBBLE:
He's just so fat, you know?
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHH!!!
Beep. Time's up.
The Squashy Grapes win.
Yeah!
So yeah, choose someone to vote.
So, um, are they gonna pick us up or what?